A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Staff Subject Files, Kilolo Kijakazi FA1848
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Working Files and Ford Foundation Initiatives, 1987-2014; 1; 37.3 Cubic Feet
  - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC), 2004-2005; 24
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) Native Americans Sault Ste. Marie, Michigan - Sault Ste. Marie Tribe of Chippewa Indians - Anouk, Susie, 2004 June 2; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15876)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) African Americans, Flint, Michigan (1 of 2) - Mission of Peace - Anouk, Susie, 2004 June 5; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15877)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) African Americans, Flint, Michigan (2 of 2) - Mission of Peace - Anouk, Susie, 2004 June 5; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15878)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) African and Caribbean Immigrants, New York - NY Work Alliance - Anouk, Susie, 2004 June 14; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15879)
      Recorded double speed
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) Pacific Islanders, Oakland, California - NEDLC - Anouk, Susie, 2004 June 26; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15880)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) Latino Americans, San Antonio, Texas (1 of 2) - Dept of Community Initiatives - Anouk, Susie, 2004 July 1; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15881)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) Ford Foundation SWB (?) Latino Americans, San Antonio, Texas (2 of 2) - Dept of Community Initiatives - Anouk, Susie, 2004 July 1; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15882)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Individual Development Account (IDA) Child Savings Account (CSA) Tax Convening, NYC, Session I, 2004 June 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15883)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Individual Development Account (IDA) Child Savings Account (CSA) Tax Convening, NYC, Session II, 2004 June 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15884)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Small Group: Latinos, 2004 May 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15885)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Small Group: African Americans, 2004 May 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15886)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Small Group: Asians, 2004 May 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15887)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Small Group: Research, 2004 May 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15888)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Small Group: Practice, 2004 May 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15889)
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Session I, 2004 May 14; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15890)
      Friday evening session.
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Session IIa, 2004 May 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15891)
      Saturday welcome and Session 1
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Session IIb, 2004 May 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15892)
      Session 1 continued.
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Session IIc, 2004 May 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15893)
      Saturday, Session 2
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Session IId and Small Group Policy, 2004 May 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15894)
      Session 2 and Small group.
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Session IIIa, 2004 May 16; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15895)
      Sunday, Session 3
    - National Economic Development and Law Center (NEDLC) and Ford Foundation Tuskegee Convening, Session IIIb, 2004 May 16; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15896)
      Session 3 and Closing.
  - Land Rich Conference, 2007 April; 25
    - Land Rich Conference: Legal and Policy Workshop, 2007 April; DVD (Box 31)
    - Land Rich Conference: Innovative Capital Workshop, DVD (Box 31)
    - Land Rich Conference, DVD 1, 2007 April 12; DVD (Box 31)
    - Land Rich Conference DVD 2, 2007 April 12; DVD (Box 31)
    - Land Rich Conference Day 2 Plenary Session, 2007 April; DVD (Box 31)
    - Land Rich Conference: Community Organizing Workshop, 2007 April; DVD (Box 31)
    - Land Rich Conference: DVD 1, 2007 April 13; DVD (Box 31)
    - Land Rich Conference DVD 2, 2007 April 13; DVD (Box 31)
    - Land Rich Conference DVD 3, 2007 April 13; DVD (Box 31)
    - Land Rich Conference: Keynote and Heirs, 2007 April; DVD (Box 31)
    - Land Rich Conference: Innovative Capital and Horace Jones, 2007 April; DVD (Box 31)
  - Tuskegee University, 2005-2010; 26
    - Asset Builders of America, 2005-2008 (Box 31, Folder 307)
    - Land Rich: How African American Communities Can Optimize the Value of Their Land Assets, undated; DVD (Box 31)
    - Tuskegee Asset Building Partners Meeting, 2009 January 8 (Box 31, Folder 308)
    - H. Dreamal Ingram Worthen, Florida AM University, and Black Belt Action Network, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 309)
    - Tuskegee University Working File, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 310)
    - Southern Regional Asset Building Conference, Closing the Wealth Gap: Promoting Inclusive Asset-Building Policy, Tallahassee, Florida, 2009 October 14-16 (Box 32, Folder 311)
    - Building a Regional Asset Building Coalition Meeting, Gulfport, Mississippi, 2008 February 10-11 (Box 32, Folder 312)
    - Tuskegee University Working File, 2006 (Box 32, Folder 313)
    - Hurricane Katrina Responses, 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 314)
    - Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco, Community Development Investment Review, Volume 2, Issue 3, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 315)
    - Meeting with Wayne Fawbush on Southern Region and Possible Overlap of Work, 2008-2010 (Box 33, Folder 316-317)
    - Ford Foundation's Community and Resource Development (CRD) Program Reserve Funds Grants, 2006-2009 (Box 33, Folder 318)
    - Ford Foundation Southeast Region Working Group, 2006-2008 (Box 33, Folder 319)
    - Grant with Jeffrey Campbell to Black Belt Community Foundation, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 320)
    - Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) - Rural Finance, 2006-2008 (Box 33, Folder 321)
    - Land-Based Grants: Collaborative Project with Ford Foundation's Community and Resource Development (CRD) Program, John W. Boyd, Jr., National Black Farmers Association, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 322)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, Center for Policy Research on Aging (CPRA), 2005-2014; 27
    Grant 10701233, 2007 August 01-2011 July 31
    For the Center for Policy Research on Aging's research on the financial status of and risks facing the aging U.S. Latino population and develop a policy agenda for improving its financial security
    - Notes and Correspondence, 2011 (Box 75, Folder 670)
    - 15th Anniversary Celebration, Aging in a Majority-Minority Nation: Interracial and Intergenerational Tensions and Opportunities, 2013 March 21 (Box 75, Folder 671)
    - Re-Framing the Generational Divide: Baby Boomers vs. Young Latinos, 2006-2011 (Box 75, Folder 672)
    - Framing the New Policy Agenda: Latino Baby Boomers in an Aging Society, 2010 May 11 (Box 75, Folder 673)
    - Latino and Economic Security Meeting, 2014 March (Box 75, Folder 674)
    - Prefunding Social Security Benefits to Achieve Intergenerational Fairness: Can It Be Done in the Social Security Trust Fund?, Randall P. Mariger, 2008 December (Box 75, Folder 675)
    - Latinos and Social Security (LSS) News Releases and Policy Briefs, 2005-2008 (Box 75, Folder 676)
    - Working Files, 2006-2013 (Box 75, Folder 677-680, Box 76, Folder 681)
      The Regents of the University of California, Los Angeles (10701233), 2007 August 01-2011 July 31
  - The Aspen Institute, 2004-2014; 28
    Core support for the Initiative on Financial Security to develop new financial products and policies that increase the capacity of low- and moderate-income Americans to save, invest and own assets
    - Lifelong Financial Security Executive Institute Meeting, 2010 October 27-29 (Box 78, Folder 697)
    - Financial Security Summit, Rebuilding Household Balance Sheets, 2012 (Box 78, Folder 698)
    - Financial Security Summit, Rebuilding Household Balance Sheets, 2013 July 7-10 (Box 78, Folder 699)
    - Initiative on Financial Security (IFS) - The Trust Index: Driving Better Banking for the 21st Century, 2012 October 4 (Box 79, Folder 700)
    - Initiative on Financial Security (IFS) - After the Financial Meltdown: Getting Americans to Save Again, 2008 December 10 (Box 79, Folder 701-702)
    - Working Files, 2004-2014 (Box 79, Folder 703-710, Box 80, Folder 711-713)
      Grant 1020-2022, Initiative on Financial Security (IFS)
      Core support for the Initiative on Financial Security to develop new financial products and policies that increase the capacity of low- and moderate-income Americans to save, invest, and own assets
    - Savings for Life: A Pathway to Financial Security for All Americans, Press Conference, Washington, D.C., 2007 May 3; DVD (Box 80)
    - Initiative on Financial Security (IFS) Board Meeting, 2006 August 17 (Box 80, Folder 714)
  - PolicyLink, 2003-2014; 29
    - Calls, 2013-2014 (Box 87, Folder 774)
    - Getting Equity Advocacy Results (GEAR), 2012-2013 (Box 87, Folder 775)
    - Map Your Agenda Chart, undated (Folder 814)
    - Pre-Conference Session for Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) Grantees, 2011 November 8 (Box 87, Folder 776)
    - Working Files, 2006-2014 (Box 87, Folder 777, Box 88, Folder 778-780)
    - Initial Conversations with Alan Jenkins and Deepak Bhargava re: Policy Communications Infrastructure, Center for Community Change, 2003-2010 (Box 88, Folder 781)
      Grantee: Center for Community Change
      Grant Dates: 2008 August 01-2010 July 31
      Grant Number: 10000983
      Grant Purpose: Support for the national campaign for jobs and income support
  - Reports, Publications, and Correspondence, 1990-2014; 30
    - Simmons College (1000-2030), 1994-2005 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      Grant Number 10002030, 2000 October 01-2004 September 30
      Support for a program of collaborative learning and organizational strengthening among six global organizaitons concerned with women-in-development
    - Evaluating Roundtable Monitoring Survey Results, Building Economic Security Over a Lifetime (BESOL) State and Regional Asset-Building Coalition Evaluation, 2013-2014 (Box 21, Folder 218, Box 22, Folder 219-220)
    - Memo Pads of Handwritten Notes (18 books), 2002 April-2008 December (Box 22, Folder 221-222, Box 23, Folder 223-224)
    - Articulation of Need for Decisionmakers of Color in the Field, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 225)
    - Papers on Savings and Culture, Race, 1990-2004 (Box 23, Folder 226)
    - Saving Circles, Rotating Savings and Credit Associations List, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 227)
    - Consumer Federation of American Theories, 1997-2003 (Box 23, Folder 228)
    - Foundation(s) and Diversity, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 229)
      Strengthening Our Attention to Diversity: Recommendations from Foundation Staff, A Report
      What Foundation Boards are Saying About Diversity, Council on Foundations
    - The Cost of Individual Development Accounts (IDAs) - Research Reports and Working Papers from the Center for Social Development, 2000-2004 (Box 24, Folder 230)
    - Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC) and Asset Building, 2000-2004 (Box 24, Folder 231)
    - Financial Institutions and Individual Development Accounts (IDAs), 2003-2005 (Box 24, Folder 232)
    - Growing the Individual Development Account Field: Universal Savings and Asset-Building Policy Initiative, Corporation for Enterprise Development, 2003 January (Box 24, Folder 233)
    - The Aspen Institute, Future Directions for the Individual Development Account (IDA) Product Research Convening, Washington, D.C., 2003 December 12 (Box 24, Folder 234)
    - Draft - Individual Development Accounts: Planning for the Future, The Aspen Institute Economic Opportunities Program, 2005 February 14 (Box 24, Folder 235)
    - Individual Development Accounts (IDA) Field Strategy Infrastructure and Resource Support Meeting, Corporation for Enterprise Development, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 236)
    - Policy Report: Recommendations from the Field: Individual Development Accounts (IDAs) as Part of Universal Asset Building System, Robert O. Zdenek and Beverly Stein, Center for Social Development, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 237)
    - Inclusion in Asset Building: Research and Policy Symposium, Going to Scale: Principles and Policy Options for An Inclusive Asset-Building Policy, Robert E. Friedman and Ray Boshara, Policy Report, Center for Social Development, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 238)
    - Profitwise News and Views: New Pathways to Scale for Community Development Finance, 2004 December (Box 24, Folder 239)
    - Lisa Mensah's Portfolio - Exit Memos, Grant Proposals, and Grant Files (Provided by Frank DeGiovanni), 2002-2004 (Box 24, Folder 240)
    - Yahonnes Cleary's Review of Assets and Savings Initiatives Summary of Ford's Asset Building Work, 2001-2004 (Box 25, Folder 241)
    - Native American Organizations and Urban Indian Centers, 2003 May 18 (Box 25, Folder 242)
    - John Phillips' Research on Tribal Colleges - Social Bonds and Social Bridges, Developing Social Capital Potential: A Final Report to the Ford Foundation, Grant 10000169, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 243)
      University of Missouri (10000169), 2000 January 01-2003 December 31
      To develop and test a model for measuring potential sources of social capital indicators for institutions of higher learning
    - Oneida Trust Funds Committee Information and Research Paper: An American Indian Social Investment System: A Sustainable Approach by Jacque Boyle, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 244)
    - Building Tribal Economies: Linking Asset Building Strategies, First Nations Development Institute, 2004 August 17-19 (Box 25, Folder 245)
    - Sault Ste. Marie Visit Ojibwe People, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 246)
    - The Report of the Native American Lending Study, Community Development Financial Institutions Fund, 2001 November; CD (Box 25)
    - Research on Native Americans and Asset Building, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 247)
    - Investor Opportunities: Strengthening Native Asset-Building Strategies Convening, Center for Social Development (CSD), July 20-21, 2005, Chandler, Arizona (Box 26, Folder 248)
    - Native Hawai'ian - Lifelong Lessons in Financial Management (LLIFM), ALU LIKE, Inc., 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 249)
    - General Background Information on Asset Building and Ford Foundation Trustees Presentation, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 250)
    - General Background Information on Asset Building, Articles, 2001-2005 (Box 26, Folder 251)
    - General Background Information on Asset Building, Individual Development Accounts (IDAs), 2003 (Box 26, Folder 252)
    - General Background Information on Asset Building, Legislation, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 253)
    - Audio from the Social Security Summit at Ford Foundation, 2010 March 12; CD (Box 26)
    - Economic Opportunity Institute (EOI) The State of Working Washington, 2011 (Box 26, Folder 254)
    - LGBT Older Adults and Reauthorization of the Older Americans Act, Policy Brief, Services and Advocacy for Gay, Lesbian, Bisexual, and Transgender Elders (SAGE), 2011 February (Box 26, Folder 255)
    - Social Security: Especially Vital to Women and People of Color, Men Increasingly Reliant, Heidi Hartmann, Jeff Hayes, Robert Drago, Institute for Women's Policy Research (IWPR), 2011 January (Box 27, Folder 256)
    - Generations United: Social Security and Futures of Children, Elders and Families, 2009-2011 (Box 27, Folder 257)
    - National Women's Law Center Fact Sheets, 2006-2011 (Box 27, Folder 258)
    - Nataional Council of La Raza (NCLR) Retirement Security for Latinos: Bolstering Coverage, etc., 2008-2010 (Box 27, Folder 259)
    - Young, Black and Secure: An NAACP Social Security Empowerment Initiative, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 260)
    - Young, Black and Secure, undated; CD (Box 27)
    - Latinos and Social Security, UCLA, 2005-2008 (Box 27, Folder 261)
    - Publications from National Academy of Social Insurance (NASI), 2005-2013 (Box 27, Folder 262)
    - Unchartered Waters: Paying Benefits for Individual Accounts in Federal Retirement Policy, Kenneth S. Apfel and Michael J. Graetz, National Academy of Social Insurance (NASI), 2005 (Box 28, Folder 263)
    - Final Report: 2005 National Seminar Series Understanding the Social Security Debate, National Press Foundation (Box 28, Folder 264)
    - Social Security: Built to Last for Generations to Come, undated (Box 28, Folder 265)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance (NASI) Social Security Fact Sheets, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 266)
    - Institute for Women's Policy Research Fact Sheets - Black Women and Social Security; Latinas and Social Security, 2011 April-May (Box 28, Folder 267)
    - Potential Impact of Social Security Reform on Employer-Sponsored Retirement Plans and Its Likely Consequences for Retirees, Report Submitted to the Ford Foundation from the Employee Benefit Research Institute, Jack VanDerhei and Craig Copeland, 2007 May 6 (Box 28, Folder 268)
    - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities - Updates on Social Security and Hispanics and Retirement Savings Accounts and Asset Tests in Means-tested Programs, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 269)
    - The Social Security Fix-It Book: Revised 2009 Edition (Center for Retirement Research at Boston College) (Box 28, Folder 270)
    - US Pension Reform: Lessons from other Countries, Peterson Institute for International Economics, Martin Neil Baily and Jacob Funk Kirkegaard, 2009 February (Box 28, Folder 271)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance (NASI) 2014 Convening Invitation for Darren Walker to Speak, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 272)
    - Ford Foundation Social Security Memos to Pablo Farias and Susan Berresford, 2004-2011 (Box 28, Folder 273)
    - Henry Aaron Emails about Social Security Blog Posts, 2010 March (Box 29, Folder 274)
    - Social Security Briefing for Luis Ubinas, 2008-2011 (Box 29, Folder 275)
    - National Academy of Social Insurance (NASI) Improving the Lives of Vulnerable Americans Through Social Security, Ford Foundation, New York, 2011 May 6 (Box 29, Folder 291)
    - Peter Orszag, Bob Greenstein, Gene Steuerle, Sheila Zedlewski on Social Security and Ford, 2008 (Box 30, Folder 292)
    - Saving and Investing Patterns Latino Focus Group, 2004 (Box 30, Folder 293)
    - Savings, Asset Building and Tax Policy Convening, 2004 June 15 (Box 30, Folder 294)
    - Southern Coalition for Social Justice - Meetings and Information, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 323)
    - Mapped Out of Local Democracy Proposal and Budget, Chris Edley, University of California, Berkeley, School of Law and University of North Carolina Proposal, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 324)
    - Information on Land Ownership, 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 325)
    - Social Security Convening Background Information, 2004-2005 (Box 34, Folder 326)
    - Social Security Grantees - Lists and Initiative Description, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 327)
    - Global Justice: Working File - Roadmap to Reform: Understanding How Social Security Changes Could Affect You, 2005-2007 (Box 34, Folder 328)
    - Global Justice - Social Security Fact Sheets, Newsletter, undated; CD-R (Box 34)
    - Employee Benefit Research Institute (EBRI) Potential Impact of Social Security Reform on Employees, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 329)
    - Center for Retirement Research: Dissemination of Social Security Fix-It Book, 2005 (Box 34, Folder 330)
    - University of California, Los Angeles Center for Policy Research on Aging, Latino Social Security Project (LSS), 2007 (Box 34, Folder 331)
    - Terry Nixon Consulting - Reports on Social Security Grantees, 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 332)
    - Urbanomics - Grant Number 1055-1107 Working File, 2005-2006 (Box 34, Folder 333)
      Urbanomics (10551107), 2005 July 01-2006 December 31
      To increase the capacity of selected organizations to disseminate factual information about the Social Security System and proposed reforms
    - Brookings Institution: Change in Scope of Work to Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC) - Grant Number 1060-0161, Data and Background Information, 2006-2010 (Box 35, Folder 334-336)
      Grant Number: 10600161
      Grant Dates: 2005 November 01-2007 April 30
      Grant Purpose: To demonstrate and evaluate a method of expanding IRA participation for low- and moderate-income people
      Grant Amount: 850,000.00; 850,000.00
    - Brookings Institution: Areas of Collaboration with Ford Foundation, 2006-2007 (Box 35, Folder 337)
    - Brookings Institution: Policy Evaluation Project, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 338)
    - Lawsuits Against HR Block about Express IRA, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 339)
    - Brookings Institution: Working File Grant Number 1060-0161, 2005-2006 (Box 35, Folder 340)
      Grant 10600161, 2005 November 01-2007 April 30
      To demonstrate and evaluate a method of expanding IRA participation for low- and moderate-income people
    - HR Block Studies, Retirement Security Project, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 341)
    - Report on 2005 HR Block Study, Retirement Security Project (Box 36, Folder 342)
    - White Paper: Improving Opportunities and Incentives for Saving by Middle and Low-Income Households, The Hamilton Project, The Brookings Institution, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 343)
    - HR Block Study, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 344)
    - The Retirement Security Project, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 345)
    - Andy Stern's Retirement Security Project of America Works, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 346)
    - Covering the Uncovered: Common Ground Recommendations to Expand Retirement Savings for American Workers, Working Report, Conversation on Coverage, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 347)
    - Covering the Uncovered: Final Report of the Conversation on Coverage, Common Ground Proposals to Expand Retirement Savings for American Workers Outcomes from an Unprecedented Six-Year Public Policy Initiative, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 348)
    - Center for Global Policy Solutions (CGPS) Working File, 2014 (Box 37, Folder 349)
    - Opportunity Agenda - Grant Proposal Forms, 2014 (Box 37, Folder 350)
    - Center for Global Policy Solutions (CGPS) Working File - Closing the Racial and Ethnic Wealth Gap, 2012-2014 (Box 37, Folder 351)
    - Howard University Center on Race and Wealth Proposal FY 2014 - Request 121917, 2010-2013 (Box 38, Folder 366)
    - Howard University Center on Race and Wealth FY 2012 - Request 118462, 2011 (Box 38, Folder 367)
    - Howard University Center on Race and Wealth FY 2012 - Request 116759, 2011-2013 (Box 38, Folder 368)
    - Howard University Working Files, 2006-2009 (Box 38, Folder 369, Box 39, Folder 370-371)
      Grant Number 10600953
      For the Department of Economics to plan a Center on Race and Wealth to prepare students of color for the asset-building field and to launch a summer institute on the racial wealth gap